Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/hui-senvoon-99492826 (LinkedIn) github.com/Zeftiroth (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Business Administration Microsoft Office JavaScript

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Malay (Limited Working)
Chinese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

React.js / Javascript - Bootcamp Python / Flask / SQL - Bootcamp HTML / CSS / JS - Bootcamp

Hui Sen Voon

Looking for Opportunities as a Full Stack Web Developer Kuala Lumpur

Summary

Versatile Assistant General Manager with 5 years of experience overseeing daily operations in the pharmaceutical cum retail industry. Decisive planner and analytical problem solver with skills in managing teams to meet objectives swiftly. Personable and collaborative demeanor demonstrated through effective communication and willingness to apply team feedback to resolve challenges.

Experience

Lapasar Full Stack Web Developer May 2021 - Present (8 months) Shah Alam, Selangor, Malaysia

Ajna Technologies SEA
Full Stack Web Developer
August 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months)
Puchong, Selangor, Malaysia

Farmasi Voon Sdn. Bhd. Assistant Manager September 2014 - October 2019 (5 years 2 months) Kuantan, Pahang, Malaysia

Star Media Group Berhad Intern March 2013 - July 2013 (5 months) Petaling Jaya, Selangor, Malaysia

Education

NEXT Academy | SEA's Best Coding/ Digital Marketing School

Computer Software Engineering · (2020 - 2020)

University of the West of England

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business Administration and Management, General · (2013 - 2014)

Taylor's University

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business Administration and Management, General · (2010 - 2013)